

## **About me**

I have a deep passion for transforming creative ideas into engaging digital experiences as a committed front-end developer. My experience in the field of web development is proof of my persistent dedication to staying on the cutting edge of business trends. With a solid background in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, I ensure that every project I work on is cutting-edge and creative by always honing my abilities to learn new frameworks and technologies.

#### **Contact Me**

- +923077705505
- arbabbhutta1213@gmail.com
- https://arbabbhutta.github.i o/arbab-portfolio/
- Hazoori Bagh Road ghnta Ghr Multan

# **Expertise Skill**

- HTML
- CSS
- BOOTSTRAP
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACTJS
- JQUERY

### **Education**

- 2016-2017 Sakims College Multan Faculty of Science Pre-**Engineering**
- 2017-2021 Bahauddin Zakariya University **Bachelor Degree of Information Technology**

# **Work Experience**

**Junior Front End Developer** 

Top Edge Technologies | July 2022-Aug 2023

- E-commerce Website
- Blog Website
- Company Portfolio Websites

#### Internee

Hello Tech Solutions | Nov 2021-June 2022

- Designed Templates
- Cloning Website
- Badge Occupied